

Vedran Olujić

Address: Grškovićeva 58, Zagreb, Croatia

e-mail: vedranolujic23@gmail.com

Contact number: +385-95-198-9904

PROFILE SUMMARY

MSc of electrical engineering & information technology with a demonstrated history in the software development industry. Experienced in software development and all major software lifecycle methodologies. Diverse technical background and skills in all aspects of software testing.

WORK EXPERIENCE

dSPACE Engineering d.o.o.

Zagreb, Croatia

Software test engineer

August 2019 – present

• Testing dSPACE FlexRay configuration package, part of dSPACE RCP and HIL software suite. Writing and executing automatic E2E regression tests in Python, automated GUI testing with C# and Ranorex, explorative testing. Test planning, debugging, documenting and specification, mentoring newcomers. Development and maintenance of test frameworks. Technologies used: MATLAB/Simulink, C, C#, Python, AUTOSAR

Ericsson Nikola Tesla d.d.

Zagreb, Croatia

Software developer

October 2017 – July 2019

Software development intern

November 2016 – October 2017

 Worked in QA and cross functional development teams in radio software department: radio software and testcase development, continuous verification and delivery, daily test execution and analysis, test system development and maintenance, delivery of script fixes, Radio software development. Technologies used: TestNG, Java, Perl, C++

GlobalLogic d.d.

Software development internship

Zagreb, Croatia July - August 2016

• Embedded C software development for ARM Cortex-M4 processors on STM32F4 development boards. Development of a home automation system.

Cei-ieta d.o.o. Zagreb, Croatia

Internship in a metrology laboratory

February - March 2016

• Translation of an oscilloscope calibration guide from English to Croatian language, calibration of various electronic devices and electrical components.

EDUCATION

MSc of electrical engineering and information technology

10/2015 -7/2017

University of Zagreb, Faculty of Electrical Engineering and Computing

- Profile: Electronic and Computer Engineering
- Master thesis: "Digitally Controlled System for Audio Input and Output Selection in Control Rooms"

BSc of electrical engineering and information technology

9/2010 - 7/2015

University of Zagreb, Faculty of Electrical Engineering and Computing

- Profile: Electronics
- Bachelor thesis: "Microphone Preamplifier"

Frank W. Cox High School (advanced diploma)

9/2007 - 6/2010

Virginia Beach, Virginia, United States

• Principal's List: 4.0 GPA student

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming languages:

- C
- C#
- Python
- MATLAB

Technologies used: Git, Gerrit, Linux, JSON, XML, Java, TestNG, Eclipse, Jenkins, Microsoft Office, Logic Pro, Keil, JIRA, Altium Designer, EASE, ARTA, MATLAB/Simulink, dSPACE RCP and HIL suite, Vector CANalyzer

OTHER SKILLS

Native language: Croatian

Second languages: English C1, German A2

Driver's license: category B

Hobbies and interests: DIY electronics, Audio engineering, Guitar, Arduino, IoT